<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TOODMING</title><link>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/</link><description>Recent content on TOODMING</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:16:43 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legacy of void</title><link>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/history/legacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:25:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/history/legacy/</guid><description>back
NationWars III He got the opportunity of participating in the tournament as the member of Mainland China. At last, he got the result of 2-4. He won two games against Cheetos and Hydra.
GPL International 2016 He got the opportunity of Gold Series International 2016 by winning Cyan in the open qualifier. Although he lost to Sioras while no one imagined it before this match started, he still won Has twice with his airdrop tactics and entered Ro8.</description></item><item><title>Heart of swarm</title><link>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/history/heart/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:24:56 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/history/heart/</guid><description>back
Transferring between several teams On March 4, 2013, TooDming announced on his weibo that he had parted ways with Answer Gaming.
On August 5, it was announced that TooDming had joined the Starcraft 2 division of Long Chen.
On December 3, TooDming leaves Long Chen, and joins Zenith of Origin.
2014 WCS America Season 1 On January 3, 2014, TooDming qualified for WCS America 2014 Season 1 Challenger League through the Chinese qualifier.</description></item><item><title>Wings of liberty</title><link>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/history/wings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:24:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/history/wings/</guid><description>back
TooDming was eliminated of 2011 Chinese Battle.net Invitational in group stage, but was yet invited to BlizzCon 2011 StarCraft II Invitational because the Chinese players who had qualified for the event could not attend due to VISA issues. In the first round of the BlizzCon, he defeated Ret despite the odds being against him, and then faced Mvp. Even though he managed to win a game against the three-times GSL champion, he was sent in loser&amp;rsquo;s bracket by his opponent.</description></item><item><title>Biography</title><link>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/biography/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:57:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://wzz1230.github.io/xiaoming/biography/</guid><description>Back
TooDming Huang &amp;ldquo;TooDming&amp;rdquo; Huiming (born July 10, 1988) is a retired Chinese Zerg player.
He was among the last professional Brood War players from China. Among others, he represented his country at the WCG 2009.
Player information Name tooDming Nationality China Born July 10, 1988 (age 33) Total earnings $145,330.71 Main achievements 2006 IEF Fujian Division Champion 2008 wgt beijing division champion 2008 wcg beijing division champion 2009 IEF Zhengzhou Division Champion 2009 wcg beijing division champion 2009 PLU StarCraft first man station third place Runner-up in the 2009 WCG China Finals Champion of WCG2010 China Wild Card Tournament 2010 IEF China Championship Champion of the second season of the 2010 G League Championship Champion of the third season of the 2010 G League Championship Champion of the fourth season of the 2010 G League Championship Winner of the Fifth Season of the 2010 G League Championship The winner of the eighth week of the 2012 Kung Fu Cup China-Korea Challenge, became the first Chinese player to win a BO7 in the Kung Fu Cup In the 2012 Kung Fu Cup China-Korea Challenge, defeated the mountain bag in BO3 in the tenth week of the 2012 Kung Fu Cup China-Korea Challenge, and became the first Chinese player to dance on the face of the mountain bag Back</description></item></channel></rss>